So let's go back to our Neural Network with our weights and our input.
回到具有权重和输入的神经网络
And recall that the weights with superscript one belong to the first layer.
具有上标 1 的权重属于第一层级
And the weights with superscript two belong to the second layer.
具有上标 2 的权重属于第二层级
Also recall that the bias is not called B anymore.
偏差不再叫做 b
Now it's called W31 W32 et cetera,
现在叫做 W31 W32 等等
for convenience so that we can have everything in matrix notation.
这样是为了用矩阵表示所有内容
And now what happens with the input?
输入会怎样？
So let's do the Feedforward Process.
我们开始执行前向反馈流程
In the first layer,
在第一层级
we take the input and multiply it by the weights and that
我们用输入乘以权重
gives us each one which is a linear function of the input and the weights.
得出 h1 它是输入和权重的线性方程
Same thing with H_2 given by this formula over here.
同样 使用这个公式得出 h2
Now in the second layer,
在第二层级
we take this h_1, h_2 and then you bias.
我们使用 h1 h2 和偏差
Apply the sigmoid function,
并应用 s 型函数
and then apply a linear function to them by
然后对它们应用线性方程
multiplying them by the weights and adding them to get a value of
将它们乘以权重并相加 得出值 h
h. And finally in the third layer we
最后 在第三层级
just take a sigmoid function of H to get our prediction.
我们对 h 应用 s 型函数 得出预测
Our probability between zero and one which is y_hat.
即在 0 到 1 之间的概率 用 ŷ 表示
And we can write this in more condensed notation by
我们可以写成更简练的形式
saying that the matrix corresponding to the first layer is W superscript 1.
第一层级对应的矩阵是 W(1)
The matrix corresponding to the second layer is W superscript 2.
第二层级对应的矩阵是 W(2)
And then the prediction y_hat is just going to be the sigmoid of
预测 ŷ 是 W(2) 的 s 型函数
W superscript 2 combined with the sigmoid of W superscript 1,
与 W(1) 的 s 型函数相结合
applied to the input X, and that's Feedforward.
应用到输入 x 上 这就是前向反馈
Now we're going to develop Backpropagation which is precisely the reverse of Feedforward.
现在我们将形成反向传播 正好是前向反馈的逆过程
So we're going to calculate the derivative of these error function with respect to
我们将使用链式法则计算这些误差函数
each of the weights in the labels by using the chain rule.
相对于标签中每个权重的导数
So we're going to calculate the derivative of the error function with
我们将使用链式法则计算误差函数
So let's recall that our error function is this formula over
我们的误差函数是这个公式
here which is a function of the prediction y_hat.
即预测函数 ŷ
But since the prediction is a function of all the weights W_I_J,
但是预测是所有权重 Wij 的函数
then the error function can be seen as the function on all the W_I_J.
那么误差函数可以看做所有 Wij 的函数
Therefore, the gradient is simply the vector formed by
因此梯度就是误差函数 E
all the partial derivatives of the error function e with respect to each of the weights.
相对于每个权重的偏导数形成的向量
So let's calculate one of the derivatives.
我们来计算其中一个导数
Let's calculate the derivative of e with respect to W11 superscript 1.
我们计算下 E 相对于 W11(1) 的导数
So since the prediction is simply a composition of
因为预测就是函数组合
functions and by the chain rule we know that
根据链式法则
the derivative with respect to this is the product of all the partial derivatives.
我们知道这一部分的导数就是所有偏导数的积
In this case, the derivative e with respect to
这里 导数 E 相对于 W11
W11 is the derivative of e with respect to y_hat,
是 E 相对于 ŷ 的导数
times the derivative of y_hat with respect to h,
乘以 ŷ 相对于 h 的导数
times the derivative H with respect to H1 times the derivative of H1 respect to W11.
乘以 h 相对于 h1 的导数 乘以 hi 相对于 W11 的导数
This may seem complicated but the fact that we can calculate a derivative of
看起来似乎有点复杂
such a complicated composition function by just
但是我们能够通过将四个偏导数相乘
multiplying four partial derivatives is remarkable.
得出这么一个复杂的组合函数 简直太神奇
Now we've already calculated the first one,
我们已经计算出了第一部分
the derivative of e with respect to y_hat.
即 E 相对于 ŷ 的导数
And if you remember we got y_hat minus y.
结果是 ŷ - y
So let's calculate out the other ones.
我们计算下其他几部分
Let's zoom in a bit and look at just one piece of our multi-layer perceptor.
稍微放大下 只看多层感知器的一个部分
The inputs are some values H1 and H2 which are values coming in from before.
输入是值 h1 和 h2 它们是来自前面的值
And once we apply the sigmoid and the linear function
对 h1 h2 及偏置单元对应的 1
on H1 and H2 and one corresponding to the bias unit,
应用 s 型函数和线性方程后
we get a result H.
得到结果 h
So now what is the derivative of H with respect to H1?
h 相对于 h1 的导数是多少？
Well H is a sum of three things and only one of them contains H1.
h 是三项的和 其中只有一项包含 h1
So the second and the third summand just give us a derivative of zero.
所以第二和第三项得出导数 0
The first summand gives us W11 superscript 2 because that is a constant.
第一项得出 W11(2) 因为这是常量
And that times the derivative of the sigmoid function with respect to H1.
该常量乘以 s 型函数相对于 h1 的导数
This is something that we calculated below in the instructor comments,
我们在下面的讲师注释中计算了这部分
which is that the sigmoid function has a beautiful derivative namely;
s 型函数拥有完美的导数
the derivative of sigmoid of H is precisely sigmoid of
即 σ(h) 的导数正好是
H times 1 minus sigmoid of
σ(h*(1-σ(h))
H. Again you can see the development underneath in the instructor comments.
你可以在下方的讲师注释中看到演算过程
You also have the chance to code this in the quiz because at the end of
你还可以在测验中将公式编写为代码
the day we just code these formulas and then use them forever.
因为最终我们会将这些公式编写成代码 然后一直使用它们
And that's it. That's how you train a neural network.
讲完了 神经网络就是这么训练的